[
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-441",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/arranging-coins/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P001_Arranging_coins.java",
    "name": "Arranging coins",
    "serialNum": 1,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-04",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-69",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/sqrtx/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P002_Find_square_root.java",
    "name": "Sqrt(x)",
    "serialNum": 2,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-22",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-268",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/missing-number/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P003_Missing_number.java",
    "name": "Missing number",
    "serialNum": 3,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-23",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Bit Manipulation", "Hash Table", "Math", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-136",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-number/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P004_Single_number.java",
    "name": "Single number",
    "serialNum": 4,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-23",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Bit Manipulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2859",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-values-at-indices-with-k-set-bits/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P005_Sum_of_values_at_indices_with_K_bits.java",
    "name": "Sum of values at indices with K set bits",
    "serialNum": 5,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-24",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Bit Manipulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1720",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/decode-xored-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P006_Decode_XORed_array.java",
    "name": "Decode XORed array",
    "serialNum": 6,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-24",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Bit Manipulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1486",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/xor-operation-in-an-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P007_XOR_operation_in_an_array.java",
    "name": "XOR operation in an array",
    "serialNum": 7,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-25",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Bit Manipulation", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1342",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-steps-to-reduce-a-number-to-zero/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P008_Number_of_steps_to_reduce_a_number_to_zero.java",
    "name": "Number of steps to reduce a number to zero",
    "serialNum": 8,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-25",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Bit Manipulation", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2220",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-bit-flips-to-convert-number/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P009_Minimum_bit_flips_to_convert_number.java",
    "name": "Minimum bit flips to convert number",
    "serialNum": 9,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-26",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Bit Manipulation"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2220",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/flipping-an-image/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/math/leetcode/P010_Flipping_an_image.java",
    "name": "Flipping an image",
    "serialNum": 10,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-26",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Bit Manipulation", "Matrix", "Simulation", "Two Pointers"]
  }
]